Hi my name is Tishambia Caine and I'm with Studio Soiree and I'm doing the cardio cabaret dance routine.
So we've done three movement and now we are going to do the second set of kicks.
It is actually the same kick but we are going to add a little bit more by bringing our arms out.
You see these muscles.
We are going to gage those by bringing those arms out.
You do this for a couple of hours and you will gain some serious muscles.
So it is just simple, bring your arms out and do the same kick but in this case go forward where the leg goes in front of the arms and then in back, in back, now this part of the routine is about control.
You have to have some serious control and then back.
Again always use your stomach to control yourself and to keep your arms up like this takes a lot of shoulder muscles, back muscles.
You will get a double work out between these arms and the legs.
So that is four movements you have just learned.